Otto Rothschild Photographic Archive LSC.1381
UCLA Library Special Collections
Otto Rothschild Photographic Archive
1930-1981
UCLA Library Special Collections
Rothschild, Otto
LSC.1381
38.0 Linear Feet (58 boxes, 8 cartons, and 484 oversize boxes)
Rothschild was a Los Angeles commercial photographer and the official performing arts photographer for the Los Angeles Music Center, Hollywood Bowl, and Philharmonic. The collection consists of Rothschild's photographs and negatives, correspondence and periodicals.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Rothschild Family, 1982-1983.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942336993606533
We are committed to providing ethical, inclusive, and anti-racist description of the materials we steward, and to remediating existing description of our materials that contains language that may be offensive or cause harm. We invite you to submit feedback about how our collections are described, and how they could be described more accurately, by filling out the form located on our website: Report Potentially Offensive Description in Library Special Collections.
Biography
Rothschild was a Los Angeles commercial photographer; he also served as the official performing arts photographer for the Los Angeles Music Center, Hollywood Bowl, and Philharmonic.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of photographs and negatives related to the career of photographer Otto Rothschild. Also includes some correspondence and periodicals.
Negatives (photographs).; Photographers -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives.; Photographs.; Rothschild, Otto -- Archives
- Negative Nos. 1001-1570, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 1)
- Negative Nos. 1571-2271, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 2)
- Negative Nos. 2272-2800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 3)
- Negative Nos. 2801-3450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 4)
- Negative Nos. 3451-3980, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 5)
- Negative Nos. 3981-4600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 6)
- Negative Nos. 4601-5150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 7)
- Negative Nos. 5151-5814, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 8)
- Negative Nos. 5815-6409, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 9)
- Negative Nos. 6410-6901, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 10)
- Negative Nos. 6902-7358, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 11)
- Negative Nos. 7359-7878, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 12)
- Negative Nos. 7879-8361, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 13)
- Negative Nos. 8362-8916, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 14)
- Negative Nos. 8917-9394, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 15)
- Negative Nos. 9395-9931, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 16)
- Negative Nos. 9932-10191, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 17)
- Negative Nos. 10192-10549, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 18)
- Negative Nos. 10550-11283, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 19)
- Negative Nos. 11284-11821, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 20)
- Negative Nos. 11822-12384, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 21)
- Negative Nos. 12386-12889, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 22)
- Negative Nos. 12890-13362, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 23)
- Negative Nos. 13363-13921, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 24)
- Negative Nos. 13922-14405, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 25)
- Negative Nos. 14406-14990, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 26)
- Negative Nos. 14991-15441, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 27)
- Negative Nos. 15442-15932, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 28)
- Negative Nos. 15933-16478, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 29)
- Negative Nos. 16479-16956, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 30)
- Negative Nos. 16957-17491, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 31)
- Negative Nos. 17492-18079, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 32)
- Negative Nos. 18080-18566, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 33)
- Negative Nos. 18567-19176, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 34)
- Negative Nos. 19177-19671, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 35)
- Negative Nos. 19672-20133, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 36)
- Negative Nos. 20134-20577, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 37)
- Negative Nos. 20578-21082, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 38)
- Negative Nos. 21123-21671, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 39)
- Negative Nos. 21672-22108, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 40)
- Negative Nos. 22109-22583, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 41)
- Negative Nos. 22584-23003, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 42)
- Negative Nos. 23004-23525, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 43)
- Negative Nos. 23526-23972, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 44)
- Negative Nos. 23973-24459, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 45)
- Negative Nos. 24460-24896, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 46)
- Negative Nos. 24897-25402, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 47)
- Negative Nos. 25404-26099, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 48)
- Negative Nos. 26100-26750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 49)
- Negative Nos. 26751-27265, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 50)
- Negative Nos. 27266-27818, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 51)
- Negative Nos. 27819-28383, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 52)
- Negative Nos. 28384-29033, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 53)
- Negative Nos. 29034-29546, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 54)
- Negative Nos. 29547-29958, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 55)
- Negative Nos. 29959-30371, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 56)
- Negative Nos. 30372-30764, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 57)
- Negative Nos. 30765-31270, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 58)
- Negative Nos. 31271-31632, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 59)
- Negative Nos. 31633-32091, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 60)
- Negative Nos. 32092-32549, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 61)
- Negative Nos. 32550-32960, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 62)
- Negative Nos. 32961-33349, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 63)
- Negative Nos. 33350-33812, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 64)
- Negative Nos. 33814-34299, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 65)
- Negative Nos. 34300-34739, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 66)
- Negative Nos. 34750-35193, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 67)
- Negative Nos. 35200-35818, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 68)
- Negative Nos. 35819-36359, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 69)
- Negative Nos. 36360-36850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 70)
- Negative Nos. 36854-37489, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 71)
- Negative Nos. 37490-38031, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 72)
- Negative Nos. 38032-38562, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 73)
- Negative Nos. 38563-39057, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 74)
- Negative Nos. 39058-39549, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 75)
- Negative Nos. 39550-40036, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 76)
- Negative Nos. 40037-40548, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 77)
- Negative Nos. 40549-41107, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 78)
- Negative Nos. 41108-41599, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 79)
- Negative Nos. 41600-41991, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 80)
- Negative Nos. 41992-42371, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 81)
- Negative Nos. 42372-42682, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 82)
- Negative Nos. 42683-43031, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 83)
- Negative Nos. 43032-43401, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 84)
- Negative Nos. 43402-43790, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 85)
- Negative Nos. 43791-44164, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 86)
- Negative Nos. 44165-44571, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 87)
- Negative Nos. 44572-44952, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 88)
- Negative Nos. 44953-45352, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 89)
- Negative Nos. 45353-45690, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 90)
- Negative Nos. 45691-46012, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 91)
- Negative Nos. 46013-46304, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 92)
- Negative Nos. 46305-46649, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 93)
- Negative Nos. 46650-47056, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 94)
- Negative Nos. 47057-47442, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 95)
- Negative Nos. 47444-47895, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 96)
- Negative Nos. 47896-48270, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 97)
- Negative Nos. 48272-48667, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 98)
- Negative Nos. 48668-49069, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 99)
- Negative Nos. 49070-49494, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 100)
- Negative Nos. 49495-50177, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 101)
- Negative Nos. 50178-50639, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 102)
- Negative Nos. 50640-51099, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 103)
- Negative Nos. 51100-51566, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 104)
- Negative Nos. 51567-51999, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 105)
- Negative Nos. 52000-52436, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 106)
- Negative Nos. 52437-52838, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 107)
- Negative Nos. 52839-53184, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 108)
- Negative Nos. 53185-53501, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 109)
- Negative Nos. 53502-53858, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 110)
- Negative Nos. 53859-54173, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 111)
- Negative Nos. 54174-54564, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 112)
- Negative Nos. 54565-54982, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 113)
- Negative Nos. 55000-55371, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 114)
- Negative Nos. 55372-55941, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 115)
- Negative Nos. 57150-57467, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 116)
- Negative Nos. 57468-57833, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 117)
- Negative Nos. 57834-58180, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 118)
- Negative Nos. 58181-58549, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 119)
- Negative Nos. 58550-58876, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 120)
- Negative Nos. 58877-59238, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 121)
- Negative Nos. 59239-59540, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 122)
- Negative Nos. 59541-59817, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 123)
- Negative Nos. 59818-60129, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 124)
- Negative Nos. 60130-60449, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 125)
- Negative Nos. 60450-60898, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 126)
- Negative Nos. 60905-61388, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 127)
- Negative Nos. 61434-61799, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 128)
- Negative Nos. 61800-62223, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 129)
- Negative Nos. 62224-62689, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 130)
- Negative Nos. 62690-63099, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 131)
- Negative Nos. 63100-63460, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 132)
- Negative Nos. 63461-63849, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 133)
- Negative Nos. 63850-64221, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 134)
- Negative Nos. 64222-64621, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 135)
- Negative Nos. 64626-64982, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 136)
- Negative Nos. 64983-65351, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 137)
- Negative Nos. 65358-65949, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 138)
- Negative Nos. 65950-66430, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 139)
- Negative Nos. 66433-67420, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 140)
- Negative Nos. 67426-67966, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 141)
- Negative Nos. 67967-68439, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 142)
- Negative Nos. 68440-69049, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 143)
- Negative Nos. 69050-69898, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 144)
- Negative Nos. 69900-70707, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 145)
- Negative Nos. 70708-71451, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 146)
- Negative Nos. 71452-72232, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 147)
- Negative Nos. 72233-73051, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 148)
- Negative Nos. 73052-73986, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 149)
- Negative Nos. 73987-74888, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 150)
- Negative Nos. 74889-75775, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 151)
- Negative Nos. 75776-76517, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 152)
- Negative Nos. 76518-77433, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 153)
- Negative Nos. 77434-78438, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 154)
- Negative Nos. 78439-79221, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 155)
- Negative Nos. 79222-79993, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 156)
- Negative Nos. 79994-80705, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 157)
- Negative Nos. 80706-81399, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 158)
- Negative Nos. 81400-82082, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 159)
- Negative Nos. 82083-82798, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 160)
- Negative Nos. 82799-83499, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 161)
- Negative Nos. 83500-84199, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 162)
- Negative Nos. 84200-84925, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 163)
- Negative Nos. 84926-85658, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 164)
- Negative Nos. 85659-86421, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 165)
- Negative Nos. 86422-87238, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 166)
- Negative Nos. 87239-88056, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 167)
- Negative Nos. 88057-88849, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 168)
- Negative Nos. 88850-89800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 169)
- Negative Nos. 89801-90550, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 170)
- Negative Nos. 90551-91350, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 171)
- Negative Nos. 91351-92250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 172)
- Negative Nos. 92251-93050, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 173)
- Negative Nos. 93051-93800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 174)
- Negative Nos. 93801-94600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 175)
- Negative Nos. 94601-95500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 176)
- Negative Nos. 95501-96300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 177)
- Negative Nos. 96301-97250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 178)
- Negative Nos. 97251-97992, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 179)
- Negative Nos. 98005-98800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 180)
- Negative Nos. 98801-99750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 181)
- Negative Nos. 99751-100550, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 182)
- Negative Nos. 100551-101300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 183)
- Negative Nos. 101301-102150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 184)
- Negative Nos. 102151-103000, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 185)
- Negative Nos. 103001-103824, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 186)
- Negative Nos. 103825-104800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 187)
- Negative Nos. 104801-105800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 188)
- Negative Nos. 105801-106950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 189)
- Negative Nos. 106951-108100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 190)
- Negative Nos. 108101-109040, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 191)
- Negative Nos. 109041-109994, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 192)
- Negative Nos. 110002-110815, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 193)
- Negative Nos. 110816-111650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 194)
- Negative Nos. 111651-112524, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 195)
- Negative Nos. 112525-113650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 196)
- Negative Nos. 113651-114550, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 197)
- Negative Nos. 114551-115380, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 198)
- Negative Nos. 115381-116225, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 199)
- Negative Nos. 116226-117025, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 200)
- Negative Nos. 117026-117884, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 201)
- Negative Nos. 117885-118779, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 202)
- Negative Nos. 118780-119615, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 203)
- Negative Nos. 119616-120431, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 204)
- Negative Nos. 120432-121250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 205)
- Negative Nos. 121251-122064, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 206)
- Negative Nos. 122065-122939, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 207)
- Negative Nos. 122940-124000, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 208)
- Negative Nos. 124001-124875, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 209)
- Negative Nos. 124876-125700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 210)
- Negative Nos. 125701-126682, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 211)
- Negative Nos. 126683-127610, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 212)
- Negative Nos. 127611-128522, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 213)
- Negative Nos. 128523-129380, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 214)
- Negative Nos. 129381-130200, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 215)
- Negative Nos. 130201-131030, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 216)
- Negative Nos. 131031-131850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 217)
- Negative Nos. 131851-132674, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 218)
- Negative Nos. 132675-133558, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 219)
- Negative Nos. 133559-134270, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 220)
- Negative Nos. 134271-135129, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 221)
- Negative Nos. 135130-136100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 222)
- Negative Nos. 136101-137000, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 223)
- Negative Nos. 137001-137750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 224)
- Negative Nos. 137751-138000, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 225)
- Negative Nos. A14-A290, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 225)
- Negative Nos. A291-A800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 226)
- Negative Nos. A901-A1347, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 227)
- Negative Nos. A1348-A1900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 228)
- Negative Nos. A1901-A2450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 229)
- Negative Nos. A2451-A3140, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 230)
- Negative Nos. A3141-A4350, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 231)
- Negative Nos. A4351-A5450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 232)
- Negative Nos. A5451-A6450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 233)
- Negative Nos. A6451-A7650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 234)
- Negative Nos. A7651-A8800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 235)
- Negative Nos. A8801-A9880, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 236)
- Negative Nos. A9881-B940, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 237)
- Negative Nos. B951-B1900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 238)
- Negative Nos. B1901-B2800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 239)
- Negative Nos. B2801-B3950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 240)
- Negative Nos. B3951-B4945, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 241)
- Negative Nos. B4951-B6000, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 242)
- Negative Nos. B6001-B7460, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 243)
- Negative Nos. B7401-B8450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 244)
- Negative Nos. B8451-B9345, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 245)
- Negative Nos. B9351-C300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 246)
- Negative Nos. C301-C1350, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 247)
- Negative Nos. C1351-C2350, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 248)
- Negative Nos. C2370-C3100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 249)
- Negative Nos. C3101-C3900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 250)
- Negative Nos. C3901-C4650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 251)
- Negative Nos. C4651-C5450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 252)
- Negative Nos. C5451-C6250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 253)
- Negative Nos. C6251-C7100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 254)
- Negative Nos. C7101-C7900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 255)
- Negative Nos. C7901-C8700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 256)
- Negative Nos. C8701-C9700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 257)
- Negative Nos. C9701-D600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 258)
- Negative Nos. D601-D1500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 259)
- Negative Nos. D1501-D2250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 260)
- Negative Nos. D2251-D3000, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 261)
- Negative Nos. D3001-D3750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 262)
- Negative Nos. D3751-D4550, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 263)
- Negative Nos. D4551-D5400, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 264)
- Negative Nos. D5401-D6150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 265)
- Negative Nos. D6151-D6950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 266)
- Negative Nos. D6951-D7750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 267)
- Negative Nos. D7751-D8500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 268)
- Negative Nos. D8501-D9350, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 269)
- Negative Nos. D9351-E100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 270)
- Negative Nos. E101-E950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 271)
- Negative Nos. E951-E1800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 272)
- Negative Nos. E1801-E2600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 273)
- Negative Nos. E2601-E3700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 274)
- Negative Nos. E3701-E4750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 275)
- Negative Nos. E4751-E5500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 276)
- Negative Nos. E5501-E6300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 277)
- Negative Nos. E6301-E7100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 278)
- Negative Nos. E7101-E7900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 279)
- Negative Nos. E7901-E8700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 280)
- Negative Nos. E8701-E9450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 281)
- Negative Nos. E9451-H200, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 282)
- Negative Nos. H201-H1050, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 283)
- Negative Nos. H1051-H1900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 284)
- Negative Nos. H1901-H2750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 285)
- Negative Nos. H2751-H3600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 286)
- Negative Nos. H3601-H4500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 287)
- Negative Nos. H4501-H5400, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 288)
- Negative Nos. H5401-H6250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 289)
- Negative Nos. H6251-H7250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 290)
- Negative Nos. H7251-H8250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 291)
- Negative Nos. H8251-H9100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 292)
- Negative Nos. H9101-H9950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 293)
- Negative Nos. H9951-L750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 294)
- Negative Nos. L751-L1500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 295)
- Negative Nos. L1501-L2350, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 296)
- Negative Nos. L2351-L3150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 297)
- Negative Nos. L3151-L4050, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 298)
- Negative Nos. L4051-L4850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 299)
- Negative Nos. L4851-L5850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 300)
- Negative Nos. L5851-L6750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 301)
- Negative Nos. L6751-L7600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 302)
- Negative Nos. L7601-L8500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 303)
- Negative Nos. L8501-L9500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 304)
- Negative Nos. L9501-N400, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 305)
- Negative Nos. N401-N1150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 306)
- Negative Nos. N1151-N1950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 307)
- Negative Nos. N1951-N2750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 308)
- Negative Nos. N2751-N3650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 309)
- Negative Nos. N3651-N4850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 310)
- Negative Nos. N4851-N5950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 311)
- Negative Nos. N5951-N7050, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 312)
- Negative Nos. N7051-N8150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 313)
- Negative Nos. N8151-N9250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 314)
- Negative Nos. N9251-P400, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 315)
- Negative Nos. P401-P1550, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 316)
- Negative Nos. P1551-P2600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 317)
- Negative Nos. P2601-P3700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 318)
- Negative Nos. P3701-P4750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 319)
- Negative Nos. P4751-P5950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 320)
- Negative Nos. P5951-P7100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 321)
- Negative Nos. P7101-P8300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 322)
- Negative Nos. P8301-PP9350, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 323)
- Negative Nos. P9351-R450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 324)
- Negative Nos. R451-R1750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 325)
- Negative Nos. R1751-R2950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 326)
- Negative Nos. R2951-R4000, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 327)
- Negative Nos. R4001-R5197, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 328)
- Negative Nos. R3709-Lytton, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 329)
- Negative Nos. R5201-R6300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 329)
- Negative Nos. R6301-R7650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 330)
- Negative Nos. R7651-R8950, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 331)
- Negative Nos. R8951-S150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 332)
- Negative Nos. S151-S1450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 333)
- Negative Nos. S1451-S2800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 334)
- Negative Nos. S2801-S4100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 335)
- Negative Nos. S4101-S5250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 336)
- Negative Nos. S5251-S6500, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 337)
- Negative Nos. S6501-S7400, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 338)
- Negative Nos. S7401-S8216, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 339)
- Negative Nos. S8217-S9550, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 340)
- Negative Nos. S9551-T550, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 341)
- Negative Nos. T551-T1600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 342)
- Negative Nos. T1601-T2600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 343)
- Negative Nos. T2601-T3650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 344)
- Negative Nos. T3651-T4700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 345)
- Negative Nos. T4701-T5800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 346)
- Negative Nos. T5801-T6850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 347)
- Negative Nos. T6851-T7951, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 348)
- Negative Nos. T7950-T8850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 349)
- Negative Nos. T8850-T9850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 350)
- Negative Nos. T9851-V250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 351)
- Negative Nos. V251-V550, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 352)
- Negative Nos. V551-V900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 353)
- Negative Nos. V901-V1300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 354)
- Negative Nos. V1301-V1600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 355)
- Negative Nos. V1601-V1900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 356)
- Negative Nos. V1901-V2300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 357)
- Negative Nos. V2301-V2650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 358)
- Negative Nos. V2651-V3050, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 359)
- Negative Nos. V3051-V3450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 360)
- Negative Nos. V3451-V3850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 361)
- Negative Nos. V3851-V4200, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 362)
- Negative Nos. V4201-V4600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 363)
- Negative Nos. V4601-V5050, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 364)
- Negative Nos. V5051-V5497, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 365)
- Negative Nos. V5501-V5900, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 366)
- Negative Nos. V5901-V6350, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 367)
- Negative Nos. V6351-V6750, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 368)
- Negative Nos. V6751-V7250, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 369)
- Negative Nos. V7251-V7650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 370)
- Negative Nos. V7651-V8096, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 371)
- Negative Nos. V8097-V8650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 372)
- Negative Nos. V8651-V9100, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 373)
- Negative Nos. V9101-V9650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 374)
- Negative Nos. V9651-W150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 375)
- Negative Nos. W151-W700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 376)
- Negative Nos. W701-W1450, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 377)
- Negative Nos. W1451-W2200, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 378)
- Negative Nos. W2201-W3050, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 379)
- Negative Nos. W3051-W3800, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 380)
- Negative Nos. W3801-W4700, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 381)
- Negative Nos. W4701-W5300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 382)
- Negative Nos. W5301-W6200, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 383)
- Negative Nos. W6201-W7148, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 384)
- Negative Nos. W7150-W8150, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 385)
- Negative Nos. W8151-W9300, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 386)
- Negative Nos. W9301-X400, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 387)
- Negative Nos. X401-X1600, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 388)
- Negative Nos. X1601-X2650, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 389)
- Negative Nos. X2651-X3850, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 390)
- Negative Nos. B6851-B7200, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 391)
- Negative Nos. B6851-B7200, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 391)
- Negative Nos. X3851-X4189, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 391)
- Negative Nos. R3709-Lytton, 4 × 5 negatives (Box 392)
- Negative Nos. B9234-L4631, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 393)
- Negative Nos. L4655-N9952, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 394)
- Negative Nos. N9953-P9949, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 395)
- Negative Nos. R35-R6466, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 396)
- Negative Nos. R6507-S3054, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 397)
- Negative Nos. S3108-T1089, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 398)
- Negative Nos. T1142-T6316, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 399)
- Negative Nos. T6320-T9999, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 400)